Amos Rose

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Contact

P Denver, Colorado

@ amos.m.rose@gmail.com

(719) 472 - 4893

amosrose.com

GitHub

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

- Front-End: Semantic HTML, CSS, Sass/Less, React, React Native, Redux, Testing-Library/React, Jest, Responsive Design, ES6+, Unit Testing, Material-UI, Styled Components
- Back-End: REST, NodeJS, Express, Knex, Jest SuperTest, SQL, SQLite3, PostgreSQL
- Editors/Plugins: Visual Studio Code, Prettier, ESLint, Snippets, Live Share
- Languages: JavaScript, Python

Education

Lambda School 2019-2020

Full-stack Web Development

Memorial Hospital School of Radiologic Technology 2007-2009

AAS Radiologic Technology

Special Interests

Internationally awarded blues dancer with experience teaching, competing, performing, and organizing at regional, national, and international events

Summary

Full-stack developer with 10+ years of experience as a healthcare professional working on cross-functional teams in high-demand environments to deliver time-sensitive services; currently seeking a role as a developer

Projects

MyDish - Full-Stack Developer

May 2020

A mobile app that helps users view, share, and save recipes with version control features **Tech stack**:

React Native | Redux | NodeJS | Express | PostgreSQL | Knex | SuperTest | Jest

- Served as a full-stack developer expanding test coverage, debugging existing features, and planning and implementing new features to meet the stakeholder's demands
- Collaborated with a cross-functional team of full-stack developers and data scientists that emphasized planning, team communication, and pair programming through problems and features

The Posh Potluck - Lead Front-End Developer

March 2020

A web app that helps users plan, share, and organize potluck events **Tech stack**:

React | Redux | Material-UI | NodeJS | Express | SQLite3

- Led a team of 3 developers to create the front end of the application
- Collaborated with back-end developers and UX designers to design and implement the application

Employment

Interventional Radiographer / Radiographer

2017 - 2020

HealthONE Colorado / National Jewish Health

 Collaborated with cross-functional teams to perform time-sensitive procedures in emergency care and outpatient settings

Surgical Radiographer

2013 - 2017

Various Health Systems

 Managed allocation of radiology department resources and personnel to meet the needs of surgical teams

Clinical Instructor / Radiographer

2010 - 2013

Memorial Health System

• Instructed and mentored students for the Memorial Hospital School of Radiologic Technology

Staff Radiographer

2009 - 2010

Memorial Health System

- Maintained national/state credentials and completed mandatory continuing education
- Discussed technical and sensitive aspects of patient care while managing expectations of procedures, processes, and results with patients